Ana Chkhaidze: As we discussed. And then once you're done, just call me and we'll move on. So
Ana Chkhaidze: okay, begin right now. Yeah, yeah. Just move. Maybe move your shoes slightly to this
Ana Chkhaidze: computer. Okay, okay, call me when you're done. Okay? So
Ana Chkhaidze: so at 1st I didn't feel any hallucination at all. For the 1st like one to 2 min, and then I start to feel those like sprinkling huge
Ana Chkhaidze: reds like red circle blacks and whites
Ana Chkhaidze: and red circles that keep blinking right in front of me, and sometimes they most of the time they do like enlarge themselves, but not all the time, and they appear for multiple times, and
Ana Chkhaidze: the second time I it was like a flat plate
Ana Chkhaidze: that's like spinning around the center
Ana Chkhaidze: for a few seconds, and then it disappeared.
Ana Chkhaidze: and then the 3rd time was those huge, a black and red circle again.
Ana Chkhaidze: and it keeps rotating and enlarge and
Ana Chkhaidze: around the screen, and I try to find them and trace them.
Ana Chkhaidze: and the last time was the
Ana Chkhaidze: circles again, and it moves in different directions for a while, and I and the size, sometimes the size changes
Ana Chkhaidze: like from small to large.
Ana Chkhaidze: And that's all I can remember from the from the experiment.
Ana Chkhaidze: cool, perfect. Oh, yeah, did you? And no. Okay, let me.